

# IRFAN FAIRUZ @ VIKY

- Freelance Developer
- Based in Malaysia
- Born in 1996

## **Professional Summary**

Highly skilled and motivated web developer with years of experience in front-end and back-end development.

Strong knowledge of HTML, CSS & JavaScript with a focus on creating responsive and UI/UX friendly websites & web applications with efficient technologies.

My main stacks are NextJS with TailwindCSS for Frontend and NodeJS with ExpressJS for Backend.

### Work Experience

#### Freelance Web Developer 2023 - 2024

#### Freelance and Open For Works

- Develop and maintain responsive websites for clients, utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript and ReactJS.
- Writing well designed, testable, efficient code by using best software development practices.
- Integrating data from various back-end services and databases.
- Gather and refine specifications and requirements based on technical needs
- Stay plugged into emerging technologies and applying them into projects.

#### Executive Warehouse Management 2020 - 2023

#### Ozwin Retailing Sdn Bhd

- Organize and control stocks to ensure inventories are maintained at optimum level consistent with usage requirements.
- Weekly stocks arrangement to all branches
- Manage and maintain company's E-Commerce sites like Lazada, Shopee, Woocommerce and Shopify
- Manage and update backend database of warehouse daily to ensure stock availability on E-Commerce sites & retail branches.

### IT Technician & PC Sale Advisor 2017 - 2020

#### Stormzone PLT

- Computer hardware installation, troubleshooting and maintenance.
- Advice and accommodate client for custom builds based on best Price-Performance ratio.
- Basic networking.
- Closing sales.

## **Education & Certifications**

Full-Stack Web

Development

Certificate 2022 - 2023 Udemy

Front-End Web Development: HTML, CSS & JS
 Front-End Frameworks: JQuery, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS & ReactJS

Back-End Web Development : NodeJS with ExpressJS

• SQL & NOSQL Databases , API and Version Control

 Authentication and Security - Handling Credentials & Designing Secure Login

#### Diploma In Management 2014 - 2017

# Astin College

- Business systems, Business ethics and Human resource management
- Forms of business organisations management processes
- Future dimensions of business opportunities in a global economy.

### Technical Skills

TOOLS FRONTEND BACKEND FRAMEWOKRS HTMI NODEJS REACTIS VSCODE **PYTHON NEXTIS** GIT & GITHUB JQUERY **IAVASCRIPT** MONGODB POSTMAN MYSOL **TAILWINDCSS** PESTICIDE RESTFUL BOOTSTRAP NPM **EXPRESSIS** CDT

















MONGOOSE

### Languages

TECHNICAL
JAVASCRIPT:
Advanced
PYTHON:
Intermediate

NON-TECHNICAL ENGLISH : Bilingual Proficiency

B.MALAYSIA :